\-->   Privacy Policy                                                                                        [Accessibility Statement](https://august.com/pages/accessibility)

Sale Extended | Shop Our 30% Off Sale For A Limited-Time

Shop new **Yale Approach™ Lock with Wi-Fi + Keypad Touch**

30-day money-back guarantee | Free Shipping in the US

Products

Smart Locks

[

Wi-Fi Smart Lock

$199.99](https://august.com/products/august-wifi-smart-lock)[

Yale Approach™ Lock with Wi-Fi

Starting at $129.99

##### NEW](https://august.com/products/yale-approach-lock-with-wi-fi)[

Smart Lock

$199.99

##### SALE](https://august.com/products/august-smart-lock-connect)

Bundles

[

Smart Door Bundles

Starting at $279.99

##### SALE](https://august.com/pages/smart-door-bundle)

Accessories

[

Connect Wi-Fi Bridge

$79.99](https://august.com/products/august-connect)[

Yale Keypad

Starting at $69.99

##### NEW](https://august.com/products/yale-keypad)[

Matching Hardware

Starting at $19.99](https://august.com/pages/front-door-hardware)

0

0

Products  

Smart Locks

[

Wi-Fi Smart Lock

$199.99

\>](https://august.com/products/august-wifi-smart-lock)[

##### NEW

Yale Approach™ Lock with Wi-Fi

Starting at $129.99

\>](https://august.com/products/yale-approach-lock-with-wi-fi)[

##### SALE

Smart Lock

$199.99

\>](https://august.com/products/august-smart-lock-connect)

Smart Door Bundles

[

##### SALE

Smart Door Bundles

Starting at $279.99

\>](https://august.com/pages/smart-door-bundle)

Accessories

[

Connect Wi-Fi Bridge

$79.99

\>](https://august.com/products/august-connect)[

Yale Keypad

Starting at $69.99

\>](https://august.com/products/yale-keypad)[

Matching Hardware

Starting at $19.99

\>](https://august.com/pages/front-door-hardware)

Smart Locks

Doorbell Camera

Accessories

Shop now

your cart is empty

Your Cart
---------

 Your cart is empty

Keep shopping

### Buying options

Some functionalities will not be available on this option.

Some functionalities will not be available on this option.

Some functionalities will not be available on this option.

Color options

### Subtotal

Quantity 1 2 3 4 5

Add to cart Add to cart Out Of Stock

### Available payment options

Be the first to know when it's back in stock.

 Notify Me 

You're on the list

Entered wrong format: name@example.com

### Subtotal

Excluding tax and shipping

### Available payment options

### Complete your smart home

$

Add to cart

Navis Paddle in Black Suede

Pair the Navis Paddle with any August Smart Lock for 100% hands-free, keyless entry. Arrive at your door with auto-unlock and easily push your door open with your hip or elbow when your hands are tied.

$34.99

Add to cart

Connect Wi-Fi Bridge

Lock and unlock your August Smart Lock remotely, right from your phone. Instantly let friends, family and home services in, even when you're not at home.  

$79.99

Add to cart

August policies and agreements

Privacy Policy

Privacy Policy
==============

### August Website & Product Privacy Policies

August, operated by Master Lock Company LLC (“August”), provides these Privacy Policies to inform website visitors and users of our products and services of the policies and procedures regarding the collection, use and disclosure of the personal data and other information that we receive when they visit our websites or use any of our products, services or applications. For ease of reading, we have distinguished website activities from our products and services.

[Privacy Policy for August Websites](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#website) LAST UPDATED \[February 22, 2024\]

[Privacy Policy for August Products & Services](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#product) LAST UPDATED \[  February 22, 2024\]

* * *

### **Privacy Policy For August Websites**

LAST UPDATED \[  February 22, 2024\]

This policy governs any websites owned or operated by August. This policy does not apply to any websites or content referencing August products owned or operated by any other party, including Master Lock Company LLC.    

**Table Of Contents:**

1. **[Information We Collect](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#1.1)**
2. [**How We Use And Store Information**](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#1.2)
3. [**When We May Share Information**](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#1.3)
4. [**Exercising Your Choices or Rights**](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#1.4)
5. [**Changes To This Policy**](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#1.5)
6. **[Contact Us](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#1.6)**

* * *

### 1\. Information We Collect

In the course of using our website, you may provide and we may collect certain personal data and other information, including: 

* Information you provide when purchasing our products or contacting customer support, which may include your name, phone number, email address, postal addresses, credit card or other billing information and any feedback.  
* Information associated with your website visit such as your IP address, mobile device identifier, cookie identifier, browser or device heuristics such as operating system, and web pages visited.  
* Information you provide when engaging with our website forms or social media sharing or other references, such as email addresses, social media handles, product feedback or testimonials, and any associated interest-based activities.  

August websites are not authorized for use by minors under 18, and we do not knowingly collect personal data from persons under the age of 18. 

**2\. How We Use And Store Information**

We use information collected through our website for the following purposes: 

* To fulfill your product or service purchases, which may include retaining your billing information for subscriptions or other purchases  
* To respond to any customer support requests you may make
* To provide, administer and improve our website or support services
* To better understand your needs and interests
* To personalize your experience
* To provide product, service or other communications
* To provide you with further information and offers from August or complementary products or services
* To administer rewards, surveys, sweepstakes, contests, or other promotional activities or events sponsored or managed by August or our business partners
* To comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes with users, enforce our agreements and protect, investigate and deter against fraudulent, harmful, unauthorized or illegal activity.

##### **Additional information about cookies and related technologies**

August and our service providers collect certain information about your visit to our website through a variety of technologies, including:

* Cookies, which are small text files that are saved by your browser when you access our Services. We and our service providers may use both cookies and pixel tags to identify that you’ve visited our website and report on your interactions. We may also use cookies to customize and improve our Services. Please see below for additional information on how cookies are used with advertising services and your choices. 
* Pixel tags (a.k.a. clear gifs or Web Beacons), which help us better manage content on our Site by informing us what content is effective. These pixel tags gifs (or other tracking technology) may also be included in or associated with e-mails or other communications that you receive from us in order to help us track your response and interests, and to deliver you relevant content and services. We may tie the information gathered by pixel tags, cookies, or other tracking technology to personal data that you have provided us. 
* Our servers automatically record certain information about how you use our website. We use this information to administer the website and analyze this information to improve and enhance the Services by expanding the content, features, and functionality and tailoring them to our users’ needs and preferences. 
* We may use third-party advertising services to either display advertising on our website or to manage our advertising on other sites.  These services will also use cookies and pixel tags in order to provide you with relevant advertising based upon your interests on other websites.  If you wish to object to this information being used for the purpose of serving you relevant ads on other websites, you may opt-out at the [DAA website here](https://optout.aboutads.info/).

##### **For visitors from the UK or European Union, the legal basis for this data processing is:**

* Performance as necessary to support a contract, including fulfilling product orders, enabling the functionality of the website, providing customer support, and notifying you of account or important product updates.  
* Our legitimate interest to process the data, including to protect the security or integrity of the website, to carry out statistical or other analysis, to understand and improve upon the Services, and to provide you with marketing or other communications about relevant products or services which may be of interest.
* With your consent for third party products or services, or with select advertising services.
* In order to comply with a legal obligation. 

##### **Information Retention**

We may store collected information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which the data has been collected and in accordance with our internal record retention schedule.  If you pre-order or purchase August products or service subscriptions from our Site, your billing and shipping address and the last four digits of your credit card information will be stored by August and our billing service providers. We will delete your personal data when the information is no longer necessary to process a request, at your request, or to manage your account or our client relationship. However, we may store any aggregate or anonymous information indefinitely.

##### **International Transfer**

August is based in the United States, where we and our service providers store the majority of our website and other collected information.  If you are a visitor or customer from the UK or EU, please note that we use a variety of legal mechanisms to protect the integrity and security of your information when transferring it to the U.S., including requiring our data service providers to agree to Standard Contractual Clauses approved by the European Commission.

You have the ability to access, modify, download or delete your personal data through the mobile application.  You may also visit our [support website](https://support.august.com/) or email us at dpo\[at\]august.com.

**Information Security**

The security of your information is important to us. We follow generally-accepted industry standards to protect the submitted to us through this website, both during transmission and once we receive it. However, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

### 3\. When We May Share Information

We may share or transfer collected information for any of the previously described purposes in these instances;

* To organizations affiliated with our parent company, Fortune Brands Innovations, Inc.
* To third party service providers who provide billing services, website functionality, facilitate communications, enable customer support and other services connected to this website or our communications, but only to the extent necessary to support our products or provide these services.
* With your consent, such as when you enable an account integration with any of the ‘works with August’ services.
* When required by law
* To a buyer or a potential future buyer of our business.

We may choose to aggregate or anonymize your information and share it with partners or others for market research or other business purposes.  

This website may contain links to other websites or services. The fact that we link to a website or service is not an endorsement, authorization or representation that we are affiliated with that third party. We do not exercise control over any of the information you provide, or is collected by, these third-party websites or services. We encourage you to read the privacy policies or statements of the other websites you visit and services that you use

.

### 4\. Exercising Your Choices or Rights

##### **Communications**

If you are a registered user, you may change your phone number or email address, and update your preferences within the mobile application in order to manage your product-specific communications. We also give you the ability to unsubscribe from marketing-related emails by clicking on a link in each such e-mail.

##### **Cookies**

To manage cookies used on the website, you may adjust the privacy settings in your browser to block them from being used or delete them from local storage. With respect to advertising services, August endeavors to work exclusively with service providers aligned with the principles adopted by the Digital Advertising Alliance. If you wish to object to this information being used for the purpose of serving you relevant ads on other websites, you may opt-out at the [DAA website here](https://optout.aboutads.info/) . Please note this does not opt you out of being served all advertising. You will continue to receive generic ads without interest-based information collected from this website.

For more information about your cookie choices on this website, refer to our cookie policy here: [Cookie Policy](https://august.com/pages/cookie-policy) .

##### **Changing or Deleting Your Information**  

If you are a registered user, you may review, update, correct or delete the information in your registration profile by logging into your account through the mobile application and changing the “user preferences” associated with their account. Removing your information may limit our ability to communicate or provide the Services to you. If you completely delete all such information, your account will be deactivated and you may lose access to the Service and your use of the device. You may also contact us at support\[at\]august\[dot\]com if you have additional questions or need additional assistance. We’ll take steps to modify or delete your information as soon as is practical, but some information may remain in archived/backup copies for our records or as otherwise required by law.

##### **For visitors from the UK or European Union, in addition to the references above, you may choose to exercise the following personal data rights:**

* Request a copy of your personal data from our records;
* Ask that we correct or erase your personal data (though this may mean that we cannot process requests, or that your account is deactivated);
* Ask us to stop processing your personal data in certain circumstances or restrict how we process it (for example if you deem the data to be incorrect);
* Request the personal data used to provide you with information you requested, or manage your account or our relationship in a machine-readable format, which you are entitled to transfer to another data controller; and
* Withdraw your consent to us processing your data for any purposes for which it was requested at any time.

We may not accept a request to modify or erase your personal data where we cannot verify your personal data, where we require it to comply with a legal obligation or in relation to a legal claim. For information about how to exercise your rights, see Contact Us below.

For California Consumers, please see California Consumer Disclosures below.

5\. Changes To This Policy

This Privacy Policy may be updated from time to time to reflect changes to our information practices. If we make any material changes we will notify you by email or other communication method. All other updates will be made through this website by means of posting an updated version of this Privacy Policy on the Site. We encourage you to periodically review this page for the latest information on our privacy practices. Any modifications to this Privacy Policy will be effective upon the date indicated in our posting of the new terms. In all of the above cases, your continued use of the website after any notice or posted modified Privacy Policy indicates acceptance of the modified Privacy Policy.

### 6\. Contact Us

For product-related privacy questions, please refer to our [Privacy Policy For August Products and Services](#product), or the extensive list of answers on our [support website](https://support.august.com/). If you have additional questions with respect to customer-related data, you may reach us by email at support\[at\]august.com. For all other privacy-related questions, please contact us at privacy\[at\]august.com or by mail at:

Master Lock Company LLC  
6744 Howell Avenue  
Oak Creek, WI 531154  
1-800-308-9244

* * *

### Privacy Policy For August Products & Services

LAST UPDATED \[February 22, 2024\]

This policy applies with respect to August products or services and owned or operated mobile apps

**Table Of Contents:**

1. **[What Personal Information do we collect?](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#2.1)**
2. [**How and why will we use your Personal Information?**](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#2.2)
3. **[Who and where will your Personal Information be transferred to](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#2.3)?**
4. [**Exercising Your Choices or Rights**](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#2.4)
5. [**Changes To This Policy**](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#2.5)
6. [**Contact Us**](https://online-store-web.shopifyapps.com/pages/53037989962#2.6)
    
    * * *

### 1\. What Personal Information do we collect?

_Personal Information We Request for Use of the Services._  When you download the App and in order to use the Services, we require you to establish an account, for which we collect and store the following: your name, email, password, telephone number, the identification number for your locksets (“Products”) and user and account verification identifiers.  

_Personal Information collected based on your use of the Services._  When you use the Services, we collect Personal Information that you may provide about yourself, such as user-name, as well as Personal Information about other people who have access to your Products, such as other family members, guests, and service providers like gardeners, house cleaners and/or others (“Invitees”).  For example, you may include email addresses and telephone numbers of Invitees who you are allowing to access your Products.  We may ask for access to your contact list, and you may consent to provide access to such list, which includes Personal Information. 

We collect Personal Information that you may include in help requests, customer service correspondence and/or in any feedback, you send to us.  We also collect Personal Information included in messages that you may send from within the App whether those messages are sent to us, an Invitee, or a third party.

Also, if you enable the Auto-Unlock feature, the App will request your consent in order to track your location in order to determine when your App nears Products that you have permission to access (e.g., when you are near home). Location information will only be stored on your device, and not on our servers. This information will tell your mobile device to start listening for your lock more often (increasing the polling). This improves the device’s performance and saves your mobile device’s battery life.

_Personal Information we automatically collect._  When you use the App, we will create a user ID for your account and we also gather the following information for purposes of providing the Services when you download the App and/or access the Services: usage data about how and when you interact with the Services and Products, logs of when your Products are locked/unlocked, logs of those who lock/unlock your Products, the people that you invite to use your Products, and those people who may invite you to use their products.

We also collect the following information about the devices on which the App is downloaded and the Products you use: the operating system of the device on which the App is downloaded (e.g., you, your invitees), the version of the App on such devices, information about your Products, including serial numbers, MAC address, software versions on such Products and installation dates. 

Additionally, if you choose to use the App to connect your Products with other products and services through the “Connected by” feature, we will collect information about your use of those other products.

**_Personal Information we receive when you use third party products and services_.** If you access the Services through a third-party (e.g., by managing your device via your television remote or connecting your device to your home security system), use third-party applications or services through the “Works With” feature, otherwise use a third party service provider in connection with the Services and Products, or request or authorize us to give access or data to a third-party service provider (e.g., a delivery service, property management or rental service), then that third party will send us data about you, such as an user ID.    

**_Invitees._**  As part of our Services, you may give Invitees permission levels to access your Products - e.g., to unlock and lock your door, and possibly even to pass this access along to others. Needless to say, you must be careful of the people that you invite and the access that you give them. You are responsible for all uses of your account, so be careful to secure this information and only give access to people you trust. Additionally, certain portions of your Personal Information, as well as other information about your use of the Service and your Products may be shared with Invitees, such as your name and the status of the lock (e.g., locked or unlocked). 

In connection with the guest invitation process, we may ask for access to your contact list. We will only store information for contacts that you add as guests. We will only access and store such information with your express consent.

If you are an Invitee, we collect your Personal Information when you use the Services and Products, as set forth in this Privacy Policy.  All such information (including your service usage information) is subject to and will be used and disclosed as set forth in, this Privacy Policy.

### 2\. How and why will we use your Personal Information? 

| **Why do we process this Personal Information?** | **What is the legal basis for processing?** |
| --- | --- |
| To provide you with the Services, including registering and management of your account, your use of the App and access to the Products you purchase, identifying/authenticating you when you use the App, providing any features and functionality in the App and the Products that you elect to use, customer service requests, maintenance which includes software updates, and communicating with you specific to the Services. | Performance of a contract (i.e. the end user agreement between you and us). |
| To personalize the Services for purposes of you signing in and using the Services and your Products. | As necessary to perform our business purposes as described in this policy and without selling your personal information |
| To ensure only you and your guests have access to the Products. | Performance of a contract (i.e. the end user agreement between you and us). |
| To carry out statistical analysis about the use of the Services and Products for purposes of making improvements. | As necessary to perform our business purposes as described in this policy and without selling your personal information |
| To send you communications and contents about relevant solutions and services, in accordance with your marketing preferences. | We will only send you relevant content where we have your consent to do so. |
| To comply with legal requirements to which we are subject, such as tax, accounting/financial reporting requirements, mandatory disclosures and/or law enforcement. | Using your Personal Information in this way is necessary for us to comply with our legal obligations. |

### **3. Who and where will your Personal Information be transferred to?** 

We will transfer Personal Information for the purposes set out above:

* To service providers to perform services necessary for us to provide the following for the Services: hosting, development, maintenance, billing services, mobile application functionality, facilitate communications/messages, customer support, and any features or functionality available as part of the Services and Products, provided only to the extent necessary to provide the Services.  This includes the processing of data concerning usage of the Services and our Products.  Any third party service providers may only use your Personal Information only according to our instructions. 
* To your Invitees when you invite them to access your Products.  For example, if you invite a guest to access your Products, then we will share certain elements of your information with them, such as your name, in order for your guest to understand the invite and access the Product.  
* To third parties that you choose when you use the “Works With” feature of the Services to connect your Products with such third party products or services.
* To affiliated entities when you use the “Connected With” feature in the App for purposes of connecting your Product with the other products and services you use.
* To organizations affiliated with our parent company, Fortune Brands Innovations, Inc.
* With your consent, such as with guest invitations or if you choose to connect our products to work in conjunction with third party products or services. See below for additional information about guest sharing. **Please note that when you consent to these transfers, any shared data will then be subject to the privacy policies of those third parties.**
* To a buyer or a potential future buyer of our business.
* As required by law.

We take measures to protect all Personal Information transferred to a third party, or to other countries, in accordance with applicable data protection laws and as stated above.

Privacy policies of other websites.
-----------------------------------

When you use the “Works With” feature in the App, you may be linked to third-party services and websites that you choose.  Also, when using the App, you may use features that link you to social media websites, such as Facebook or Twitter.  We are not responsible for the privacy practices or content of any of these third parties or the linked sites. Linked sites may collect Personal Information from you that is not subject to our control. We encourage you to review the privacy policies on any linked website you visit.

**Information Retention**

We may store collected information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purpose for which the Personal Information has been collected, and in accordance with our internal record retention schedule. If you purchase August products or the Services, your billing and shipping address and the last four digits of your credit card information will be stored by August and our billing service providers. Lock activity is stored alongside your account information for the duration of your account being active. Doorbell camera photos and videos are available for download through our mobile application for up to thirty (30) days or as referenced in the selected subscription terms of service, unless the information is necessary to be preserved based on a valid law enforcement obligation.

We will delete your personal data when the information is no longer necessary to process a request, at your request, or to manage your account or our client relationship. We will continue to store mobile application use and lock activity, including guest activity, for a period of at least ninety (90) days following account deletion.

We may store any aggregate or anonymous information indefinitely.

### 4\. Exercising Your Choices or Rights

**_Right to know personal information collected_**

You have the right to know which personal information has been collected from you.

**_Right to say no to the sale of personal information_**

Our vendors use cookies on our websites as described in Section 2 above, which may constitute a “sale” under applicable law. For information on how to opt-out of the use of cookies for marketing or other purposes, please see the Cookies Section above. August could share your personal information with service providers and with other August associated entities for the purposes described herein. You have the right to know which personal information is disclosed and to whom.  The service providers and other August associated entities perform processes on behalf of August.

**_Right to access and rectification_**

You have the right to request access to the personal information relating to you. This includes the right to be informed, whether or not personal information about you is being processed, what personal information is being processed, and the purpose of the processing.

You can self-exercise your rights in the following situations:

**_Communications_**\-   If you are a registered user, you may change your phone number or email address and update your preferences within the mobile application in order to manage your product-specific communications.

**_Mobile Data:_** If you access the Service through a mobile device and you do not want your mobile device to provide us with location-tracking information, you can disable the GPS or other location-tracking functions on your mobile device. See your mobile device manufacturer’s instructions for further details. Of course, if you do this, Service functionality (such as the Auto-Unlock feature described immediately above) may not work.

**_Right to deletion_**

You may request that your personal information be deleted in certain circumstances.

We also give you the ability to unsubscribe from marketing-related emails by clicking on a link in each such email

Please note that we may reject your request if the processing is permitted or required according to a law or any other relevant legal ground.

Product owners are always responsible for the photos, videos, and other personal data captured of their guests, and August provides no remediation for guests to remove photos, videos or other personal data from our systems unless expressly authorized by the registered account of the product owner.

**_Right to obtain equal service, even if they exercise their privacy rights._**

We do not discriminate against any individual who exercises the rights mentioned. You are entitled to exercise your rights without prejudice to receive different services in quantity or quality.

**_Children’s Privacy_** 

The “**service”** is Not for or Directed to Children nor anyone under 18 years old; we do not intend to and will not knowingly collect any personal data from children under the stated age. If we learn that we have collected personal data from an under the age of 18, we will remove that personal data immediately and delete it from our servers (if not required or resulted by applicable law and this Privacy Notice). If you believe content from an under 18 years has been posted in our **“service,”** please notify us by contacting us at customerservice@mlock.com.

**NOTICE TO CANADIAN RESIDENTS**

If you are a resident of Canada, these additional terms apply to our collection, use and disclosure of personal information. Any reference in this Privacy Policy to “personal data” should be understood to refer to “personal information” under applicable Canadian privacy laws. 

**Consent:** By submitting personal data to us, or our service providers and agents, you consent to the collection use, disclosure, and transfer of your personal data, including transfers outside of Quebec, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and as permitted or required by law. 

**Access and Correction:** Upon your written request, and subject to certain exceptions provided by law, we will inform you of the existence, use, and disclosure of your personal data and give you access to that information. We may charge a minimal fee for providing such access to you. If you are able to establish that the information is not accurate or complete, we will take reasonable steps to delete and/or correct the information so that it is accurate, complete, and up-to-date. You may make these requests by calling 1-800-308-9244 or e-mailing us your request to customerservice@mlock.com. We may verify your request by using a third party identity verification service. Any such information will only be used for the purpose of confirming your identity and will not be retained by us. Please note that, for your safety and to protect your privacy, we cannot fulfill certain requests if we cannot verify your identity.  Further, please make any privacy related requests or inquiries by calling 1-800-308-9244 or e-mailing us your request to [customerservice@mlock.com](mailto:customerservice@mlock.com).

**_California Consumer Disclosure_**

The terms “Business Purpose(s)”, “Personal Information”, “Sell” (or “Sale”), “Service Provider(s)” and “Third Parties” have the meanings given in the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (CCPA).  These term references and disclosures are limited to this section of the Privacy Policy and designated exclusively for California Consumers. The disclosures detailed above are fully incorporated in this California Consumer Disclosure.

**Categories of Personal Information** - Unique browser or device identifiers such as cookies, mobile ad IDs (IDFAs for iOS and Android Ad IDs), device hardware identifiers, timestamps, user agent strings, IP addresses, and precise geographic location data. See the disclosures above for additional details. 

**Purposes for collection and use of Personal Information -** We use personal information to facilitate our mobile applications, hardware devices, customer account services, and for marketing or communications. See the disclosures above for additional details. 

**Categories of sources from which Personal Information is collected -** Websites, mobile applications, advertising services, technology platforms, and customer support services. See the disclosures above for additional details. 

**Categories of Personal Information we sell -** Our vendors use cookies on our websites as described above, which may constitute a “sale” under applicable law. Please see below for further details. For information on how to opt-out of the use of cookies for marketing or other purposes, please see the Cookies Section above.

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| **_Category of Personal Information_** | **_Categories of Recipients_** |
| Internet and electronic network activity information | Companies which provide advertising and marketing services |

**Purposes for selling personal information -** Our vendors use cookies on our websites as described above, which may constitute a “sale” under applicable law. Please see above for further details.  For information on how to opt-out of the use of cookies for marketing or other purposes, please see the Cookies Section above. See the disclosures above for additional details. 

**Categories of Third Parties to whom Personal Information is sold -** Our vendors use cookies on our websites as described above, which may constitute a “sale” under applicable law. Please see above for further details.  For information on how to opt-out of the use of cookies for marketing or other purposes, please see the Cookies Section above. See the disclosures above for additional details. 

**Categories of entities to whom information was disclosed for a business purpose -** Advertising services, technology platforms, website and mobile application analytics.

Subject to certain limitations, you have the right to (1) request to know more about the categories and specific pieces of personal information we collect, use, and disclose, (2) request deletion or correction of your personal information, and (3) not be discriminated against for exercising these rights. You also have the right to request that we not sell your personal information or to limit the processing of your sensitive personal information (to the extent applicable). The California Consumer Privacy Act allows California residents \\ to obtain from us twice a year, free of charge, information regarding the categories and specific pieces of personal information we collect, use, and disclose, as well as the purposes for such processing, and the parties to whom we may disclose such information in the preceding 12 months.

For more information about interest-based ads, or to opt out of having your web browsing information used for behavioral advertising purposes, or to exercise your right to opt-out of the sale of your information, please visit [www.aboutads.info/choices](https://www.aboutads.info/choices). If you are a California resident, you may make a request **with “California Privacy Rights” as the title of your letter, please mail it to 6744 S Howell Avenue, Oak Creek, WI 53154.**  We may verify your request by asking you to provide information about yourself and past history. We will not discriminate against you if you exercise your rights under the CCPA.

### 5\. Changes To This Policy

We may update this privacy notice from time to time in response to changing legal, regulatory, or operational requirements. We will take appropriate and feasible steps to notify users of any such changes (including when they will take effect). The latest version of our Privacy Notice is available through our website.

Your continued use of the **“service”** after any such updates take effect will constitute acceptance of those changes. If you do not accept any updates to this privacy notice, you should stop using this digital **“service.”**

### 6\. Contact Us

**August** is responsible for the processing of your personal data, and requests to exercise your rights as stated above shall be addressed to **Master Lock Company LLC 6744 S Howell Avenue, Oak Creek, WI 53154 or** [**customerservice@mlock.com**](mailto:customerservice@mlock.com)

**Toll-free**: **1 (800) 308-9244**

**February 2024**

pop-up content starts

Compare Smart Locks

|  Wi-Fi Smart Lock |  Yale Approach™ Lock with Wi-Fi |  Smart Lock + Connect Wi-Fi Bridge |  Smart Lock |
| --- | --- | --- | --- | --- |
| Wi-Fi Built In to Lock |  |     |     |     |
| Wi-Fi Bridge Included |     |  |  |     |
| Remote Access (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |  |  |     |
| Works with Siri + HomeKit |  |     |     |     |
| Works with Amazon Alexa (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |  |  |     |
| Works with Google Assistant (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |  |  |     |
| Buy $199.99 | Buy $129.99 | Buy $199.99 | Buy $149.99 |

 Wi-Fi Smart Lock

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Wi-Fi Built In to Lock |  |
| Wi-Fi Bridge Included |     |
| Remote Access (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Works with Siri + HomeKit |  |
| Works with Amazon Alexa (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Works with Google Assistant (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Buy $199.99 |

 Yale Approach™ Lock with Wi-Fi

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Wi-Fi Built In to Lock |     |
| Wi-Fi Bridge Included |  |
| Remote Access (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Works with Siri + HomeKit |     |
| Works with Amazon Alexa (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Works with Google Assistant (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Buy $129.99 |

 Smart Lock + Connect Wi-Fi Bridge

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Wi-Fi Built In to Lock |     |
| Wi-Fi Bridge Included |  |
| Remote Access (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Works with Siri + HomeKit |     |
| Works with Amazon Alexa (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Works with Google Assistant (Requires Wi-Fi) |  |
| Buy $199.99 |

 Smart Lock

|     |     |
| --- | --- |
| Wi-Fi Built In to Lock |     |
| Wi-Fi Bridge Included |     |
| Remote Access (Requires Wi-Fi) |     |
| Works with Siri + HomeKit |     |
| Works with Amazon Alexa (Requires Wi-Fi) |     |
| Works with Google Assistant (Requires Wi-Fi) |     |
| Buy $149.99 |

pop-up content ends

#### Let's stay connected.

Email 

Submit  

By signing up for the August Home US and Canada email newsletter, you agree with our [terms](https://august.com/pages/terms-of-service).

##### Products

##### Company

##### Customers

##### Partner

##### Privacy

© August Home. Designed in San Francisco, California. \*Note: Our smart locks and app are for use in the US and Canada only.
